

Sanboncheon-ro 119-9, Gunpo-si, GyonugGi-do, 15816, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-3659-8205 | Ich2895@naver.com | □ CH\_Lee

"Hope for the world."

# Summary.

I'm Changhun Lee, who want to become Robot Engineer. My research interests are wearable robot(Soft exoskelton, Hard exoskelton, etc.) for muscle strength and rehabilitation, HRI, Manipulator, Medical Robot, Control System and Firmware. I would like to help disabled people with my technology and make a world where everyone can be happy.

### Research Interest\_

Wearable Robot Soft & Hard Exoskelton

HRI Haptic

Medical Robot Surgery Robot & Manipulator

## Education

**KwangWoon University** 

Seoul, S.Korea

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022(Expected)

**B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS** 

• Total GPA: 4.12/4.50 Major GPA: 4.32/4.50

• Club: BARAM(Robotics Academic Group) - [2020 Club president]

# Work Experience \_\_\_

#### KIST(Korea Institute of Science and Technology)

Seoul, S.Korea

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2021

STUDENT INTERN(ADVISOR DR. DONGHYUN HWANG)

- · Research on HaptiCube.
- Research on Pose estimation with magnetic sensor
- · Participate in Smartfarm auto-driving system Project

Sunduck High school Seoul, S.Korea

Jun. 2020 - Sep. 2020 TEACHER

- Firmware Software Education(Arduino).
- 3D modeling Education.

### Honors & Awards\_

#### **AWARDS**

2019.12 Finalist, [17th] The World Embeded Software Contest 2019 Seoul, S.Korea

2020.08 3rd Place, Cham-bit Award Kwangwoon univ.

2020.08 Top, The first semester of the third grade Seoul, S.Korea

#### **HONORS**

2020.09 Full tuition Scholarship, For Top seat last semester Seoul, S.Korea

### Skills\_\_\_\_

**Programming** C/C++, Python, Matlab **CAD Software** Solidworks, Catia

DevOps ROS

Languages Korean, English

JUNE 14, 2021

# **Extracurricular Activity**

#### **Smart Factory with autocharge-scheduling**

Seoul, S.Korea

HARDWARE MODELING & DESIGN CLOSE LOOP CONTROL SYSTEM

May. 2019 - Dec. 2019

- 17th The World Embedded Software Contest 2019 project.
- · A system for efficiently operating a mobile robot used in a factory in consideration of the remaining battery, workload, etc.
- Modeling mobile robots, factory and Designing Close loop System to Control System.
- The source code related to this project is on my **Github**.

#### Smart Walker[Cham-bit award]

Seoul, S.Korea

Dec. 2019 - Oct. 2020

HARDWARE MODELING & DESIGN CLOSE LOOP CONTROL SYSTEM

KwangWoon Univ.'s Cham-bit award project.

- I wanted to prevent traffic accidents for the elderly.
- Walker to ensure the safety of the elderly people.
- Regardless of the terrain, it speeds up at a constant speed.
- The source code related to this project is on my **Github**.

**Javis** Seoul, S.Korea

Personal Project Aug. 2020 - Nov. 2020

- Mobile manipulator for helping disabled people.
- To implement more diverse behaviors, The manipulator has 6DOF.
- To study ROS, all systems are implemented in ROS.
- The source code related to this project is on my **Github**.

HaptiCube Seoul, S.Korea

KIST PROJECT Aug. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- I implement simulations for interaction between HaptiCube and people.
- · Based on OpenGL, there is a version that utilizes Computer Vision and a version that is based on visual effects.
- The source code related to this project is on my **Github**.

SmartFarm Seoul, S.Korea

KIST PROJECT

- Creating a auto-driving robot to help Korean melon farm workers.
- All systems are implemented in ROS.
- To help farmers, we made a mobile robot with various functions.

Magnet Pose Estimation Seoul, S.Korea

KIST PROJECT Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- We implement a magnet sensor system to follow the location of continuum mechanism.
- We conducted a study to process and analyze Magnet's data and use it for Pose Estimation.

#### **Next Generation Wireless Vehicle Charging Robot**

Seoul, S.Korea Mar. 2021 - Jun. 2021

Sep. 2020 - Nov. 2020

• We implement a Omnwheel mobile robot to wirelessly charge the electric car.

- Create a mobile robot using Cascade Motor Control.
- · All systems are implemented in ROS.
- The source code related to this project is on my **Github**.

# **Publication**

CAPSTONE PROJECT

#### INTERNATIONAL

2020.12

**IEEE TMECH 2021,** Development of an Embedded Sensor System for a 5-DOF Finger-wearable Tactile Interface, by Byeongkyu Lim, Changhun Lee, Donghyun Hwang

IEEE/ASME TMECH

JUNE 14, 2021